classiccars.com 2016-06-20

# Legal

Back to top

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We believe that a full disclosure of our privacy policy is essential to our success and to your ongoing patronage. To make this Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be voluntarily supplied or requested. 

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on _ClassicCars.com_ (the "Site"). 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Collector Car Network, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on the Network. 

In order to use certain features of the Site, such as posting a vehicle listing or subscribing to a newsletter, you must first complete a registration form and create a user account and password. During registration you provide us with your contact information (such as your name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on the Site in which you have expressed interest. 

We may give you the option to provide basic demographic information (such as income, gender, and education) to us; we strongly encourage you to submit this information so we can provide our customers with a better, more useful experience on the Site. Providing any such demographic information is entirely optional and is identified as such at the time of data collection. 

**Orders**  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order forms. You must provide contact information (such as name, email address, billing address, and shipping address) and financial information (such as a credit card number and expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to process your orders. We also use this information to send you confirmations and updates of your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

**Surveys or Contests**  
From time to time we may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on the Site. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as your age and ZIP code). 

We use this information to gather feedback about Site features, notify contest winners and award prizes, and/or to send participants an email newsletter. 

We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; any such company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice. 

**"Send to a Friend"**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the Site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and for tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us using our "Contact Us" form to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**Communications from Us**  
We will occasionally send you information on new Site features, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-Out" below for more information. 

If you wish to subscribe to our email newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe with each newsletter we send you. 

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications because they are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email and/or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

**User Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, server log files, tracking images, and third party sources to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, including your purchase history, to information in the profile, in order to provide you with tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the Network for you. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third-party sources. Examples of such sources include the following: 

_Payment Verification_  
For your protection as well as ours, we use a third-party payment processing service to verify your billing address when we process your orders. We may also use a third-party verification service in order to safeguard against fraudulent credit card use. 

_Enhancement of Profile Information_  
We may purchase marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers in which we think you would be interested. To enrich user profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personally identifiable information they have provided to us. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We share aggregated demographic information about our visitors with our partners, affiliates, and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users; rather, it provides our partners, affiliates, and advertisers with a description of our user base as a whole. Partners may include third parties with whom we have or may have a business relationship, such as sponsors. 

We share personally identifiable information with select third parties: 

_Agents_  
We use a shipping company to fulfill orders for goods, and we use online payment processing companies to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

_Fulfillment Providers_  
We use third parties to fulfill orders for certain goods and services. These companies may retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information subject to their own privacy policies. 

_Service Providers_  
We use a third party to provide email newsletter mailings. When you sign up for a newsletter, we will share your email address and certain elements of your Profile as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us. 

**Choice and Opt-Out**  
We provide you with the opportunity to "opt out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for an account with us but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our registration form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent or service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

**Log Files**  
As is typical of professionally managed websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data for each user of the Site. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track users’ movements around the Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

Generally, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are, however, tied to personally identifiable information in conjunction with orders in order to help prevent online payment fraud. 

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and tracking images to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors in the aggregate. We use this information to supplement the information we gather from analyzing our log files. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not store any personally identifiable information in cookies, but we may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information when required for technical reasons, such as in keeping track of your account information or shopping cart. 

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s documentation. More information about cookies can be found by following this link: <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WWW_cookie>

We set a persistent cookie to help keep track of visits our users make to the Site. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on the Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Site, but your ability to use many areas of the site will be limited. 

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Collector Car Network, Inc. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other third parties. Some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) use cookies on the Site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. Please see "Third Party Advertisers" for more information. 

**Tracking Graphics**  
We and/or our third-party partners employ a software technology called tracking graphics (a.k.a. "Web beacons" or "Web bugs") that help us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. Tracking graphics are tiny, transparent images with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, tracking graphics are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. As with cookies, we may tie the information gathered by tracking graphics to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use tracking graphics in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt out of these emails, you may do so by following the instructions included in every such communication. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
Some of the ads appearing the Network are delivered to users by one or more advertising partners. We may share aggregate website usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on the Site. Third-Party advertisers may use cookies and/or tracking graphics on the Site, allowing them to recognize a user when a user visits the Site. The information that such companies collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

**Links to Other Websites**  
This privacy Policy applies only to information collected by ClassicCars.com, Inc. The Site contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Co-Branded Sites**  
Portions of the Site may include content or information provided by reputable third parties and integrated into the Site by means of frames. Frames divide your Internet browser's screen into separate areas for purposes of making navigation or use of the Site easier. If you submit any information on such pages, your information is made available to that third party for purposes of providing you with the information or service you request. In such instances, it may not be obvious whether we or the third party are collecting your information. We will identify any pages of the Site that involve the framing of third-party websites. Generally, no personally identifiable information is shared on such pages. You may choose to not provide any information to the third party by navigating away from such areas of the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected on those sites. 

**Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms**  
If you use a bulletin board or chat room on the Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update, or deactivate it by making the change on our member account pages. 

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on the Site, we encrypt that information using secure sockets layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link: [ttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer)

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on the Site, you may ask via our "Contact Us" page. 

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Collector Car Network, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using our "Contact Us" page and mention our privacy policy in your inquiry. 

Back to top

Welcome to ClassicCars.com! By accessing this website (the "Site") or by making an offer on a vehicle listed on ClassicCars.com, you agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions appearing in this document. Please read the following terms and conditions carefully. Your use of the services provided by the Site or any of its subsidiaries (the "Service") is specifically conditioned upon your agreement to the Terms and Conditions contained in this Terms and Conditions Agreement (the "Agreement"). By using the Service, you are agreeing to all of the terms contained in this Agreement. 

**Definitions**  
Throughout this Agreement, the words "we," "us," "our", and "ours" refer to Collector Car Network, Inc. an Arizona corporation, its officers, employees, consultants, and subsidiaries. The words "you," "your," and "yours" refer to you, a user of the Service. 

**Modifications to Agreement**  
We may at any time, and without notice, modify, update, or otherwise change the terms of this Agreement, and you agree to be bound by such changes. Accordingly, we encourage you to visit the Site from time to time to review the current Terms and Conditions. 

**ClassicCars.com**  
ClassicCars.com is a vehicle listing, information service and auction website that brings together buyers and sellers. ClassicCars.com is not an automobile broker or dealer and does not sell, exchange, buy, or offer for sale, negotiate or attempt to negotiate, a sale or exchange of an interest in any vehicle listed for sale on our service. ClassicCars.com does not hold or possess title for any vehicle listed for sale on our service. ClassicCars.com is not a party to any vehicle sale contract between vehicle buyers and sellers that originates on or through the Service, and ClassicCars.com does not offer other ancillary products and services such as vehicle financing, service contracts, mechanical breakdown insurance, vehicle registration/titling, and vehicle transfer escrow services. 

**Ownership**  
Any and all intellectual property rights associated with the Service and the Network and its affiliates—including without limitation any inventive concepts, know-how, publicity rights, trademarks, trade dress, trade secrets, and copyrights—are the sole property of Collector Car Network, Inc., and may not be copied, reproduced, modified, uploaded, transmitted, or distributed in any way without our written permission. Except as provided herein, we do not grant to you any express or implied rights to our intellectual property. Any rights associated with content that is transmitted, downloaded, or otherwise processed by the Service shall be retained by the content owner, if any, and may be protected by applicable copyright, trademark, or other laws. For the purposes of this Agreement, the term "Content" refers to any of the various information, files, data, and media types which can be sent, received, or processed by the Service in accordance with a variety of protocols, including, without limitation, text, graphics, video, audio, streaming media, e-mail, chat, HTML, instant messaging, and the like. This Agreement gives you no rights in and to such Content. To the extent that you own any rights in Content that you provide to us, you hereby grant to us a non-exclusive, irrevocable, royalty-free, paid-up license to use, copy, publish, distribute, publicly perform, publicly display, create derivative works or otherwise exploit any Content that is provided during your use of the Service. 

"Drive Your Dream" is a service mark of Collector Car Network, Inc. "Safe-n-Secure" is a trademark of Collector Car Network, Inc. No license to use or reproduce these marks or other marks on the Service is given or implied. All other brands and product names are the trademarks of their respective owners. 

**Termination**  
You agree that we, in our sole discretion, may terminate your use of and access to all or a portion of the Service, and remove and discard any Content within the Service, for any reason, including, without limitation, for lack of use, or if we believe that you have violated this Agreement. You agree that any termination of your access to the Service may be effected without prior notice, and acknowledge and agree that we may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information, Content, or other files in your account and/or prevent any further access to such files or the Service. Further, you agree that we shall not be liable to you or any third party as a result of our termination of your access to the Service. 

**Acceptable Use**  
In consideration for your use of the Service, you agree to provide true, current, accurate, and complete information about yourself as requested, and to update such information as may be necessary to keep it true, current, accurate, and complete. You agree that you will use the Service in a manner that complies with all applicable laws, and you acknowledge that you are solely responsible for any Content that you upload, download, transmit or otherwise process using the Service. 

You explicitly agree not to:  

  * Transmit any data, text, video, audio, software, or other Content that is offensive, obscene, pornographic, inflammatory, harassing, threatening, tortious, invasive of another's privacy, abusive, hateful, defamatory, harmful to minors, or is otherwise objectionable;
  * Transmit any Content that infringes any patent, trademark, copyright, rights of publicity, or other intellectual property right;
  * Transmit any Content that violates any applicable local, state, national, or international law that could give rise to civil or criminal liability;
  * Transmit any unsolicited promotional Content, advertising materials, "spam," chain letters, unauthorized links to other websites, or other such solicitation;
  * Use the Service to publicly broadcast, transmit, or display Content for "pay-per-download" or other commercial purposes;
  * Transmit any Content that solicits purchase of any product or service, unless that solicitation has been paid for by you and explicitly approved in writing by us;
  * Use the Service to transmit Content that includes any virus, worm, Trojan horse, sniffer, or other code designed to acquire information about other users or disrupt the functionality or availability of any computer program, database, the Service or any other Internet host;
  * Disguise your identity by spoofing, forging headers, using third-party relayers, or otherwise obscuring the origin of transmitted Content, including impersonating another person or entity;
  * Use any robot, spider or other automatic or manual device or process to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Service, nor act as a conduit for others to affect the same result; or
  * Use the Service with the intent to defraud us, any user of the Service, or any other party, including, but not limited to, using the Service to solicit sales fraudulently or using the Service to engage another party in a fraudulent transaction.

**Sellers and Buyers**  
ClassicCars.com is not responsible for incorrect information given by buyers or sellers, including title and other information regarding vehicles, including but not limited to, vehicle mileage, history, condition, and photos of the vehicle. We do not guarantee nor provide warranty regarding vehicles available from our Site. The sale of vehicle(s) is between the legal owner and the buyer only. ClassicCars.com does not own, verify, buy or sell any vehicles listed for sale on our Site. ClassicCars.com does not possess title, nor hold title for any vehicle for sale on our Site. Vehicle information or inspection reports provided by sellers is provided for informational purposes only. ClassicCars.com is not responsible for any incorrect information or mistakes. 

**Make an Offer Option**  
From time to time ClassicCars.com may offer for sale a vehicle under a program which permits prospective buyers to “make an offer” using facilities made available for that purpose on the Site. Buyer activity for vehicles offered under this program are subject to additional terms and conditions as defined herein. 

When described as a “make an offer” sale, the buyer agrees that any and all offers made pursuant to this program are binding and cannot be cancelled by the buyer. Buyers agree to pay the full amount of the agreed-upon sales price to the seller in full within five (5) business days upon agreement of a sales price. Unless agreed to beforehand in writing, buyers agree the seller is not responsible for any shipping or delivery fee. Buyer agrees to pay a buyer's fee to ClassicCars.com. The buyer’s fee is five percent (5%) of the total agreed-upon sales price and is not included in the final offer price. Buyer agrees to pay all applicable government fees and taxes for the vehicle. 

**Vehicle Pricing**  
The prices listed by sellers on ClassicCars.com exclude government fees and taxes, registration and titling fees, regulatory and electronic processing charges, inspection charges, emission testing charges, and any other fees required by law, any or all of which may be added to the listed price to arrive at the final sale price of a particular vehicle. All dollar amounts listed on the website are in U.S. funds. 

**No Liability**  
We assume no responsibility for Content downloaded, uploaded, stored, or otherwise processed by the Service. Accordingly, if you choose to use the Service, you do so at your own risk. For example, you acknowledge that: 

  * Any Content you transmit will be treated by us as not being confidential to you, except as noted in the Privacy Policy;
  * You are aware of the limitations of security, authentication, encryption, and privacy measures used in connection with the Internet, including the Service, and that any Content you store or transmit may be damaged, corrupted, "sniffed" and/or accessed by another person without your permission; we cannot and will not guarantee the security of any of the Content stored or transmitted by the Service; and
  * You may be subjected to email, instant messages, video, and other Content which is pornographic, defamatory, hateful, or otherwise objectionable to you.

IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, CORRUPTION OF CONTENT, AND LOSS OR INACCURACY OF INFORMATION), ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE OR SOFTWARE, WHETHER OR NOT SUCH DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE AND EVEN IF WE WERE ADVISED THAT SUCH DAMAGES WERE LIKELY OR POSSIBLE. 

Errors in Content, including, but not limited to, description, photography, or typographical errors, are subject to correction at our sole discretion. 

**Third Parties**  
Parties other than us and our subsidiaries may operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines on the Service. Additionally, the Service may offer links to the websites of affiliated companies and certain other businesses. We shall not be responsible for examining or evaluating, and do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals or the content of their respective websites. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions, product, and content of all these and any other third parties. You explicitly agree to carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use. 

**Electronic Communications**  
By using the Service or by communicating with us electronically via email, instant messenger, or by other means, you consent to receive communications from us electronically. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. 

**Product and Service Descriptions**  
We attempt to be as accurate as possible with respect to product and service descriptions. However, we do not warrant that product and service descriptions or other Content of the Service is accurate, complete, reliable, current, or error-free. If a product or service offered by us itself is not as described, your sole remedy is to return it in unused condition subject to the terms of our Refund Policy. 

**No Warranty**  
THE SERVICE COVERED UNDER THIS AGREEMENT IS PROVIDED "AS-IS" AND "AS-AVAILABLE" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW OR OTHERWISE GOVERN THE SCOPE OF EXCLUSIONS OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY IN FULL. WE AND OUR AFFILIATES DO NOT WARRANT THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, ERROR-FREE OR VIRUS-FREE. 

**Indemnity**  
You agree to indemnify and hold us and our vendors, service providers, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners, and employees, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the Service, any Content you submit, transmit, or download through the Service, or any violation of this Agreement or the rights of others. 

**Modifications to Service**  
We reserve the right at any time to modify, correct, or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. We may also change your priority of access to the Service with respect to other users. We make no commitment to update the information provided by the Service. 

**Disclosure of Content**  
Although we have no obligation to monitor the Content of our users, we reserve the right to monitor, retain, delete and/or disclose your Content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal requirements, respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third parties, or protect our rights, property, or personal safety, or that of our users, or of the public. 

**Privacy Policy**  
For detailed information regarding our use of registration data and other user information, please read our Privacy Policy. 

**Miscellaneous**  
This Agreement shall constitute the complete and exclusive agreement between you and us. While we reserve the right to modify this Agreement at any time, the terms and conditions contained in this Agreement may not be modified by you unless both you and a representative authorized by us execute a separate written agreement. If any provision of this Agreement is held to be unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be reformed only to the extent necessary to make it enforceable, and such decision shall not affect the enforceability of such provision or of the remaining provisions of this Agreement. This Agreement shall be subject to and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Arizona, without regard to conflicts of law provisions, and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts residing in the State of Arizona. Any and all unresolved disputes arising under this Agreement shall be submitted to arbitration in the State of Arizona. The arbitration shall be conducted under the rules then prevailing of the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may obtain equitable relief in any court to protect our intellectual property. 

Back to top

By placing an order for a vehicle listing (the “Listing”), you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions appearing in this Listing Agreement. Please read the following terms and conditions carefully. Your use of the services provided by ClassicCars.com (the "Service") is specifically conditioned upon your agreement to the terms and conditions contained in this Listing Agreement (the "Agreement"). By using the Service, you are agreeing to all of the terms contained in this Agreement. 

**Definitions**  
Throughout this Agreement, the words "we," "us," "our", and "ours" refer to Collector Car Network, Inc., an Arizona corporation, its officers, employees, consultants, and subsidiaries. The words "you," "your," and "yours" refer to you, a user of the Service who has, will have, or has in the past created a Listing on ClassicCars.com. 

**Modifications to Agreement**  
We may at any time, and without notice, modify, update, or otherwise change the terms of this Agreement, and you agree to be bound by such changes. Accordingly, we encourage you to visit ClassicCars.com from time to time to review the current Listing Agreement. 

**Approval by ClassicCars.com**  
Your Listing is subject to review and approval by us, and we reserve the right to edit, modify, and/or cancel, at our sole discretion, your Listing, in part or in whole, if we determine that it is in violation of any terms of this Agreement. Availability of your Listing on the Service is not an indicator of approval; only a confirmation email message from us indicating initial approval constitutes evidence of approval. You may change most elements of your listing, such as photos, description, and vehicle details, at any time; however, any changes you make to your Listing are also subject to approval by us. 

**Cancellation of Listing**  
Your Listing stays online until you notify us that your vehicle has been sold or is otherwise no longer available for sale. However, out of concern for the quality and timeliness of the Service for all users, we reserve the right to cancel your Listing on your behalf if we have reason to believe that you have abandoned your Listing (for example, you have not logged into your account or have failed to respond to repeated requests via email over a period of six [6] months or more). 

**Renewal of Featured Listing**  
If you purchase a Featured Listing upgrade, you understand that Featured Listing status expires at the end of the purchased term unless you renew it in advance. 

**Private Parties Only**  
ClassicCars.com Premium Vehicle Listings are intended for use by private parties for the purpose of offering one (1) vehicle for sale. All dealerships must open a dealer account. 

**Acceptable Listing Content**  
Your Listing must offer one (1) vehicle for sale. Your listing must not contain any inappropriate content as defined herein. You explicitly agree not to: 

  * Use offensive, pornographic, or defamatory language or photographs
  * Include photographs, graphics, email addresses, website addresses, URLs, hyperlinks, HTML markup, or any other content other than plain text in your Listing, with the sole exception of your Listing's photographs
  * Offer or make reference to more than one vehicle per listing
  * Offer parts, accessories, or services individually or separately from the vehicle offered in the Listing
  * Modify the year, make, or model of the Listing once it has been approved by us

**Limitations of Responsibility**  
You explicitly agree that you, the seller, are wholly responsible for the successful sale of your vehicle. There is no guarantee that your vehicle will be sold or that prospective buyers will contact you. Furthermore, it is entirely your responsibility to exercise all due caution in executing transactions with any party; we make no representations as to the identity, trustworthiness, creditworthiness, or truthfulness of any prospective buyers. We are not responsible for email messages lost in transit, nor for those rejected or redirected by spam filters. Messages from member accounts identified by our internal anti-fraud systems as being at high risk for fraud may not be delivered. 

**Refund Policy**  
Due to the nature of the services we provide, we cannot provide refunds; all sales are final. 

**Applicability of Terms and Conditions**  
Your Listing is subject to the ClassicCars.com Privacy Policy and to the terms and conditions described in the ClassicCars.com Terms and Conditions Agreement, both of which are hereby incorporated by reference.
